this episode of Real Engineering is
真实工程的这一集是
brought to you by brilliant
由辉煌带来给你
a problem solving website that
一个解决问题的网站
teaches you to think like an engineer
教你像工程师一样思考
The United States military has the
美国军方拥有
strongest and most diverse Navy in the world
世界上最强大最多样化的海军
the U s military's fleet of
美国军队的舰队
aircraft carriers is so large
航空母舰那么大
it makes the U s Navy the second
它使美国海军成为第二个
largest air force in the world
世界上最大的空军
second only to the actual U S Air Force
仅次于实际的美国空军
a single Nimitz class aircraft
一架尼米兹级飞机
carrier like the USS Ronald Reagan
像罗纳德·里根号航空母舰这样的航母
a 6.2 billion dollar nuclear powered ship
一艘62亿美元的核动力船
can carry twice the aircraft as
可以携带两倍的飞机
any other foreign carrier
任何其他外国承运人
which makes it even more shocking that it
这让它更令人震惊
was sunk by a single diesel powered Swedish
被一辆瑞典柴油车击沉
submarine during war games in 2,005
2005年战争演习中的潜艇
a single submarine that cost the same as a single F35
一艘潜艇，价格与一艘F35相同
at $100 million managed to sneak by an entire
1亿美元偷偷溜走了整个
carrier task force with anti submarine defenses to
拥有反潜防御的航母特遣部队
enter the red zone and score multiple torpedo hits on
进入红色区域并获得多枚鱼雷命中
the US Ronald Reagan sinking it virtually before
美国罗纳德·里根几乎以前就击沉过它
shrinking back into the vast ocean undetected
退回到广阔的海洋而不被发现
this was just one of many exercises where the
这只是许多练习中的一个
Swedish Gotland class submarine proved too
瑞典哥特兰级潜艇也被证明
stealthy for the world's strongest navy
世界最强海军的隐形
the new submarine proved so threatening that the U s
新潜艇被证明是如此具有威胁性，以至于美国
military leased the Swedish sub for an additional year
军方把瑞典潜艇再租了一年
to develop strategies to counter the silent threat
制定应对无声威胁的策略
so what set the Gotland apart from other subs
那么是什么让哥特兰号与其他潜艇不同呢？
submarines primary instrument to
潜艇主要仪器
detect enemy subs is sonar
探测敌方潜艇是声纳
sonar is essentially a finely tuned ear that
声纳本质上是一个微调的耳朵
works like a whale's or dolphin's echo location
就像鲸鱼或海豚的回声定位
to create a 3d map of the ocean around it
创建周围海洋的3d地图
there is active sonar where the submarine
潜艇所在的地方有主动声纳
will send out a sound pulse called a ping
会发出一种叫做ping的声音脉冲
and listen for the reflections
倾听倒影
but in warzone this isn't a sound strategy
但在战区这可不是个好策略
as the ping is detected by enemies
由于ping被敌人检测到
to give your exact location
提供您的确切位置
so passive sonar is used where no ping is emitted
所以被动声纳用于没有ping信号的地方
and instead you simply listen
相反，你只是听着
these electronic ears are so accurate that the
这些电子耳朵非常精确
nationality of submarines can be determined
潜艇的国籍可以确定
based on the operating frequency of the
基于工作频率
alternating current used in its power systems
电力系统中使用的交流电
the 60 hertz alternating current of a US sub
美国潜艇的60赫兹交流电
could be differentiated from the 50 hertz of
可以从50赫兹的
European subs if the transformers and other
欧洲潜艇如果变压器和其他
electronics were not adequately insulated from the hull
电子设备没有与船体充分绝缘
the Swedes managed to create a submarine so silent
瑞典人设法制造了一艘如此安静的潜艇
that it was practically undetectable by passive sonar
被动声纳几乎无法探测到它
so how did they do this at such a low cost
那么他们是如何以如此低的成本做到这一点的呢？
the Golland was the first submarine in the world to
戈兰号是世界上第一艘潜艇
use a Stirling engine as its power generator
使用斯特林发动机作为发电机
Stirling engines are not a new concept with the first
斯特林发动机并不是第一个新概念
being created and patented by Robert Stirling in 1816
由Robert Stirling于1816年创造并获得专利
inspired by a series of high pressure steam boiler
灵感来自一系列高压蒸汽锅炉
explosions at the beginning of the Industrial
工业初期的爆炸
Revolution
革命
Stirling wanted to create a safer engine
斯特灵想制造一个更安全的引擎
that did not require such high pressures
不需要这么高的压力
I can't be Aris trying to animate this old drawing
我不可能是Aris想让这幅旧画动起来
so let's go for something simpler
所以让我们试试更简单的方法
he did this by creating a closed cylinder containing
他通过创造一个封闭的圆柱体来做到这一点
a fixed mass of gas permanently sealed within
永久密封在内部的固定气体
here  one side of the piston cylinder has a large
这里活塞缸的一侧有一个大的
buffer space which allows for a relatively
缓冲空间，允许相对
constant pressure on this side of the piston
活塞这边的恒压
while the other side fluctuates in
而另一边在波动
pressure due to alternating heating cycles
交替加热循环引起的压力
when heat is applied to the outside of the
当热量施加到外部时
cylinder the pressure increases causing the
气缸压力增加导致
piston to move until the pressure equalizes
活塞移动直到压力平衡
now if we cool the outside of the cylinder
现在如果我们冷却圆柱体的外部
with a heat exchanger the pressure will drop
使用热交换器，压力会下降
and once again the piston will move
活塞将再次移动
this is our basic pressure cycle
这是我们的基本压力循环
to create mechanical work
创造机械工作
but this is an insanely inefficient system
但这是个极其低效的系统
as most of the energy we put into the system
因为我们投入系统的大部分能量
as heat is lost during the cooling cycle
因为热量在冷却循环中流失
not to the gas
没油了
but the actual cylinder wall which
但实际的气缸壁
provides no mechanical work
不提供机械工作
Robert Sterling solved this by adding a displacer
Robert Sterling通过添加置换器解决了这个问题
piston which can drive the gas from one end of the
活塞，可以从一端驱动气体
cylinder to the other allowing this end to be
圆柱体到另一端，允许这一端是
permanently hot and the other to be permanently cold
永久热，另一个永久冷
so the cylinder wall is no longer
所以缸壁不再
experiencing a temperature cycle
经历温度循环
the pressure cycle here works slightly differently
这里的压力循环略有不同
first  the air on the hot end expands and causes the
首先，热端的空气膨胀并导致
displacer to move into contact with the power piston
位移器移动到与动力活塞接触
displacing more air from the cold
将更多的空气从寒冷中排出
end to be heated and expanded
末端加热膨胀
allowing work to be done on the power piston
允许对动力活塞进行工作
the air on the hot end now has nowhere to go
热端的空气现在无处可去
and so is driven to the cold end where it is
所以被驱赶到寒冷的一端
cooled and contracts causing work to be done
冷却和合同导致工作完成
once again on the power piston
再一次在动力活塞上
this is our new pressure cycle
这是我们新的压力循环
the efficiency of this system can be increased
这个系统的效率可以提高
further by placing what is essentially a heat battery
进一步通过放置本质上是热电池的东西
in the tubes between the hot and cold cylinders
在冷热缸之间的管子里
this conserves a huge amount of heat that would
这保存了大量的热量
otherwise be wasted during the cooling cycle and gives
否则在冷却周期中被浪费并给出
the heat back to the air as it travels back through
热量在空气中传播
Robert Stirling dubbed this the regenerator
Robert Stirling称其为再生器
now we have the foundations of a useful engine
现在我们有了一个有用引擎的基础
by incorporating a coolant
通过加入冷却剂
system and a heating chamber
系统和加热室
we create a larger temperature
我们创造了更大的温度
differential to drive the engine
差速器驱动发动机
and the efficiency can be further
而且效率可以更进一步
increased by increasing the number of
通过增加数量增加
tubes connecting the hot and cold spaces
连接冷热空间的管道
along with the number of regenerators
以及再生器的数量
and adding fins to increase the surface area of
并添加鳍片以增加表面积
these tubes to allow for heat transfer
这些管子允许热传递
did I say simplified  sorry
我说了简化的抱歉吗？
I meant easier to read
我的意思是更容易阅读
maybe I like the misery  1
也许我喜欢痛苦1
Sterling engines ultimately fell into
英镑发动机最终落入
obscurity as stronger steel became
随着钢铁变得越来越坚固
available to make steam engine boilers safer
可使蒸汽机锅炉更安全
but have seen a resurgence in recent decades with the
但近几十年来，随着
Gottland being the most famous implementation
哥特兰是最著名的实现
Scotland uses two Stirling engines that use
苏格兰使用两台斯特林发动机
diesel and liquid oxygen to provide heat which
柴油和液氧提供热量
in turn runs its 75 kilowatt generators
反过来运行75千瓦的发电机
these generators can run an electric motor
这些发电机可以驱动电动机
directly or charge batteries that can
直接或给电池充电
provide a huge boost in speed when needed
在需要时提供巨大的速度提升
all the while the exhaust is
排气一直在
compressed and stored on board
压缩并存储在船上
allowing the sub to stay
让潜艇停留
submerged for up to two weeks
浸没长达两周
vastly longer than any other diesel powered submarine
比任何其他柴油动力潜艇都长得多
so why is it so silent compared to other submarines
那么为什么与其他潜艇相比它如此安静呢？
it doesn't require much explanation as to why an
不需要太多解释为什么
internal combustion engine using tiny controlled
使用微型控制的内燃机
explosions for power tends to lead to some noise
电力爆炸往往会导致一些噪音
while the multi billion dollar nuclear powered
而数十亿美元的核动力
submarines need to pump huge volumes of coolant to
潜艇需要泵入大量冷却剂
their reactors to prevent a meltdown causing enough
他们的反应堆以防止熔毁造成足够的
noise to be detectable by passive sonar within a
被动声纳可探测到的噪声
certain range
一定范围
on top of this
在此之上
recently declassified intelligence suggest that
最近解密的情报显示
Russian submarines are using these instruments
俄罗斯潜艇正在使用这些仪器
to detect the faint trail of radiation left in
来探测留下的微弱辐射痕迹
the wake of these nuclear powered submarines
这些核动力潜艇的尾流
giving the Swedish submarine
给瑞典潜艇
another way of avoiding detection
另一种避免被发现的方法
this is a fascinating application
这是一个令人着迷的应用程序
of the laws of thermodynamics
热力学定律
understanding and applying the laws of science is the
理解和应用科学规律是
closest to a real life superpower in this world
最接近现实生活中的超级大国
so why not unlock your superpower of
所以为什么不释放你的超能力
understanding the universe by taking this
通过这个来理解宇宙
course on astronomy on brilliant
天文学课程
this course will take you from learning about the
本课程将带您了解
tools astrophysicists use to observe the universe
天体物理学家用来观察宇宙的工具
through to the calculations that will allow you to
通过计算，可以让你
peer into the future of the universe
窥视宇宙的未来
brilliant is a problem solving website that
辉煌是一个解决问题的网站
teaches you to think like an engineer
教你像工程师一样思考
you can dive in and start learning about a huge
你可以潜入并开始学习一个巨大的
range of topics starting from basic physics and
从基础物理开始的主题范围和
working your way up to more complicated topics
继续处理更复杂的主题
to support re engineering and
支持再造和
learn more about brilliant
了解更多关于辉煌
go to brilliant
出彩
org slash re engineering and sign up for free
org slash重新设计并免费注册
the first 73 people to sign up with this link will
使用此链接注册的前73人将
get 20% off their annual premium subscription
获得20%的年度保费订阅折扣
I get to learn and solve these kinds of
我要学习和解决这些问题
problems for a living and I love it
以问题为生，我喜欢它
it gives me that warm
它给我温暖
glowy feeling inside when I finally
当我终于感受到内心的光辉
conquer a difficult problem
攻克难题
actively challenging your brain on a daily
每天积极挑战你的大脑
basis and getting that endorphin rush of a job
基础和得到内啡肽匆忙工作
well done is great for your mental health
做得好对你的心理健康很有好处
brilliant even have an app where you
太棒了，甚至有一个应用程序，你可以在其中
can challenge yourself on the go  as always
可以一如既往地在旅途中挑战自己
thank you to my patrons and thank you for watching
感谢我的赞助人，感谢您的收看
if you'd like to join the real engineering community
如果你想加入真正的工程社区
I've recently set up a subreddit where we
我最近建立了一个subreddit，我们
discuss everything engineering related and more
讨论与工程相关的一切等等
the link for that is in the description
描述中的链接。